populareverything.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy – Popular Everything

Zippor Ltd. (“Zippor”) com understands that protecting the privacy of those who visit its website, is of great importance. This is the reason why we are taking the necessary steps to ensure the privacy of those who visit our website (the “ **Site** ”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and supervises the way that information is gathered on the Site and the use that is made of such information. By using the Site, you are consenting to the conditions that appear in this policy.

#### **Collecting information**

Zippor might collect personal identification details such as your email address, your name, your residential/work address or your phone number. In addition, Zippor might collect anonymous demographical information which is not unique to you – such as your area code, age, gender, preferences, and areas of interest.

In addition, information regarding your computer hardware and software is gathered automatically. This information could contain your IP address, the type of browser, names of site/users, access times and references to other internet sites. This information will be used by Zippor to activate services, to carry out quality control of the services and to provide general statistics relating to the use of the Site.

Please bear in mind that to the extent that you provide personal identification information, or personally sensitive information of any kind through the public channels on the Site, this information could be collected and used by other people.

**Remark**  – Zippor does not read private online communications. Zippor strongly recommends that you review the privacy declarations of the sites to which connect from the Site, so that you will be able to see how these sites gather, use and involve other people, in your information.

#### Use of your personal data

Zippor collects and uses your personal data for the purpose of running the Site and to provide services which you request. Zippor also makes use of your identification details to bring to your notice other products and services which are available to you on the Site and its add-ons. Zippor may also make contact with you through surveys in order to get your opinion about its existing services and about new or potential services which it may offer you in the future. 

Zippor does not sell, hire or rent out its customer listings to any third parties. Zippor may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of its external business partners regarding special offers which could be of interest to you. In that circumstance, the personal identification details which are unique to you (such as your email address, name, address, phone number, etc.) are not given to any third parties. In addition, the Zippor Site may share information with reliable partners when obtaining their assistance with statistical analysis, contacting you by email or post, providing support to customers or arranging shipment. None of these third parties are allowed to use your personal identification details other than for the purpose of providing services for the Site and must respect the confidentiality of your details.

Zippor does not use or share sensitive identification information such as ethnicity, religion or political leanings without your specific consent.

Zippor protects information and carries out a follow-up of the sites and internet pages on the Site which our customers visit, in order to identify what services on the Site are the most popular. This information is used to send personalized content and advertising from the Site to customers whose activity suggests that they are interested in specific subjects.

The Site will hand over your personal details without giving you notification, only if it is required to do so by a legal authority or when it genuinely believes that doing is necessary in order to: (a) to comply with the demands of the law or to cooperate with legal proceedings being conducted on the Site; (b) to protect and defend the rights and property of the Site; (c) to operate under circumstances of extreme emergency to protect the integrity and security of the Site’s users or of the general public.

#### **Using cookies**

The Site uses “Cookies” to help you achieve a personally matched online experience. Cookies are text files located on your hard disc by the server. Cookies cannot be used to run software or to introduce viruses on to your computer. Cookies are adapted to you uniquely and can be activated only by the server that is operating the file on your computer.

One of the main purposes of Cookies is to facilitate time-saving. The objective of Cookies is to tell the site server that you have revisited a particular internet page. For example, if you have personally verified pages on the Site or registered for the Zippor Site or for its services, the Cookie helps the Site to retrieve personal data concerning other visits made there. This simplifies the process of documenting your personal data such as billing address and shipment address, etc. When you go back to that Site the information you provided previously can be collected and you will be able to make simple use of the features offered on the Site which you have personally authenticated.

You have the choice of whether to accept or reject Cookies. Most computer browsers are programmed by default to automatically allow Cookies, but in general, it is possible to change the browser option and refuse to accept cookies – if that is your preference. If you refuse to accept cookies, it is possible that you won’t be able to experience all the features and services offered you on the Site or on the other sites you visit.

#### **Targeting  and advertising cookies** 

These Cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make as much as possible advertising relevant to you and your interests. This information is then used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests as detailed below. These cookies can be placed by Zippor or third parties including advertising networks. These cookies remember which websites you have visited and this information can be shared with other organizations such as advertisers. These cookies and the relating data processing is subject to the privacy and cookie policies of those third parties.

#### **Interest-Based Advertising**

By using Targeting and advertising cookies, Zippor and/or any other third party on our behalf may provide advertisements to you based on your recent browsing behavior across different websites, browsers, or devices. For the purpose of targeting advertisements to you for services and/or products in which Zippor will determine, in Zippor’s sole discretion, you might be interested, we may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), HTML5 local storage and other technologies.

We may also use third parties such as network advertisers, which are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to websites you have visited target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested.

Third-party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may also use cookies and/or the mentioned technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third-party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one.

#### **Your  Choices and Opting Out**

Zippor supports initiatives of greater transparency and control for users and offers the following options for controlling the interest-based content and ads you might receive. If you do not want to receive interest-based ads displayed by Zippor or by any other third party on its behalf, you can disable the display of such ads by clicking on the opt-out button below.

Once You will opt-out of tracking, your personalized content recommendations based on your Internet use history will be revoked.

Because our tracking mechanisms operate at the device and browser level, to fully opt-out across devices, you will need to do so on each device and browser individually.

One can also opt-out of receiving targeted ads served by Zippor or other advertising companies.

You may use the [NAI opt-out tool](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices), which will allow you to opt out of seeing targeted ads from us and from other NAI-approved member companies, and for mobile opt-outs, the NAI provides instructions to engage system-level opt-outs in Android, iOS, and Windows Phone environments. 

Users in the United States, Canada, and Europe may go to the DAA consumer choice page at [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices), or the DAAC consumer choice page at [www.youradchoices.ca/choices](http://www.youradchoices.ca/choices), or the EDAA consumer choice page at [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by companies listed on the DAA, DAAC, or EDAA, consumer choice pages.

Opting out from one or more companies listed on the DAA, DAAC, or EDAA consumer choice page will opt you out from those companies’ delivery of targeted content or ads to you, but it does not mean you will no longer receive any advertising through our Services or on other websites.

You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextually based ads). Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit the DAA, DAAC or EDAA consumer choice pages, your opt-out may not be effective. Additional information is available on the DAA’s website at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/), on the DAAC’s website at [www.youradchoices.ca](http://www.youradchoices.ca/), and on the EDAA’s website at [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

You may also opt out of receiving targeted ads from other third-party ad networks. You may use the [DAA opt-out tool](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/), which will allow you to opt out of seeing targeted ads from us and from other companies that adhere to the DAA principles.

Please note that opting out will not prevent you from seeing our ads on other websites, but it will affect the types of ads that you will see. These ads will no longer be tailored to your interests and instead will be chosen based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e. contextually based ads).

If your browsers are configured to reject cookies, your opt-out may not be effective, since we identify your choice to opt-out based on a cookie we deliver to you. In this case, you will need to confirm that your browser is configured properly in order for the opt-out to be effective. If you are using a Safari browser on iOS11 or macOS High Sierra, you must first adjust your Privacy and Security Settings to turn off both “Prevent Cross-Site Tracking” and “Block All Cookies”, and then return to this privacy policy or your preferred opt-out platform to reset your opt-out preferences. 

Zippor may use non-cookie technologies in limited cases. Like cookies, these technologies allow Zippor to recommend ads that are tailored to your interests and to remember whether you have chosen to opt-out of our Services. Please note that some web browsers may not permit you to block the use of non-cookie technologies, but you can do so by simply clicking on the Opt Out feature available in the “User Choices” section on this page.

#### Your personal data protection

We review this Privacy Policy regularly and reserve the right to make changes at any time to take account of changes in our business and legal requirements. We will place updates on our website.

Please take a look at the “ _LAST UPDATED_ ” date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy to see when it was last revised.

#### Contact us

The Site welcomes any comments you make about this Policy. If you believe that Zippor is deviating from its Policy, please contact us at info@zippormedia.com– we will do everything is in our reasonable power and commercial capacity to attend to the problem immediately.

**Last updated: 11/3/2018**
